(忆往昔)
-到底是谁  -利维坦
- Who the hell! - Leviathan!
我们做朋友吧  你和我
Let's be friends, you and I.
我宁愿在垃圾堆里打滚
I'd sooner swim through hot garbage
也不要和你这种下贱的怪物握手言和
than shake hands with a bottom-feeding mutation like you.
鲍比
Bobby!
你到底是什么
What the hell are you?
他是上帝的先知
He's a prophet of the lord.
-那就是神之语了  -没错
- That's the word of god? - Yes.
利维坦是什么
What's "Leviathan"?
你能认出来
You can read it?
你好  凯文
Hello, Kevin.
杀死利维坦唯一的方法是
The only way to kill Leviathan
用淋过三种堕落之血的骨头
is with the three bloods of the fallen --
堕落天使的血
Fallen angel blood.
一个始祖的血
You got to bleed an Alpha --
接下来是堕落人类统治者的血
And blood from the ruler of fallen humanity.
孩儿们好
Hello, boys.
-你愿不愿意给我们血  -乐意
- You gonna give us the blood or not? - Happily.
但目前不乐意
But not quite yet.
-那要什么时候  -到最后
- Well, then when? - Last.
好在咱们还能找克劳力  是吧
It's a good thing we got Crowley in our corner. Right?
看来最后总是得靠他
Seeing as how it all comes down to him.
肯定万无一失了
What could possibly go wrong?
-克劳力先生  -你好
- Mr. Crowley. - Hello.
(如今)
-你喝多少  -多倒
- How do you take it? - Alcoholic.
有事快说  有屁快放
Shall we get on with this, then?
就是想一尽地主之谊
Just extending the hand of hospitality.
招待我这样的怪物
To a mutation like me?
不想在垃圾堆里打滚了  是吧
Tired of swimming in hot garbage, are we?
那时真有意思  是吧
That was a little colorful, huh?
我当时没有冒犯你的意思
Didn't mean to offend.
你就是那个意思
Of course you did.
你突然召唤我过来
So, if you're suddenly calling,
我猜你已经知道温家双煞的动向了
I guess you're up to speed on the Winchesters,
这说明你抓了那位先知
Which means you intercepted the prophet.
而先知告诉你
And the prophet told you
我的血是解决一切问题的关键
that my blood is the key to everything.
知道我喜欢你哪一点吗
You know what I like about you?
不装相吗
Lack of pretension?
你比看上去聪明
You're smarter than you look.
你这话就是在调戏我
Oh, well, now you're just flirting.
杀我不容易  不过可行
Not easy...to kill me, but doable.
尤其是对于你们而言
Especially for you lot.
你们连天使都能杀
You kill angels.
除掉一个恶魔自然不在话下
You can certainly wipe a demon off the board.
而现在我们却坐在这里
And yet, here we are,
像一般的疯子一样谈判
negotiating like proper psychopaths.
我猜你在某处藏了一小瓶自己的血
Well, I assume you have a vial of your blood stashed somewhere,
一旦你死了
and in the event of your death,
这瓶血就会直接送到萨姆和迪恩手上
it goes directly to Sam and Dean.
瞧  很聪明的假设
See? Smart assumption.
人不能光靠漂亮脸蛋活着
One can't live on looks alone.
我提一下我的条件
Here's my offer.
洗耳恭听
All ears.
我对你和你的族类予以全部赦免
Full immunity for you and your constituency.
我指的是对所有恶魔类都不加干涉
I'm talking free-range grazing for all demonkind.
我愿意把戒备线划到加拿大
I'm willing to cordon off, say, Canada.
你和族人可以在那儿做做生意
You and your crew can work your little deals,
对当地人下手
have your way with the locals.
整个加拿大吗
All of Canada?
都归你们了
Have it.
好
Fair.
那这边呢
And down here?
美国人归我们
America's ours.
你的销售团队靠边站  就这么定了
Your sales team stays out -- period.
这个没得商量  我们需要美国人
That's not up for negotiation. We need America.
他们肥肉多
They're so fat.
有什么交换条件
And in exchange?
一位新泽西平凡恶魔的血
The blood of one sadly unimpressive demon in New Jersey.
我只要求你把这个交给疯傻二兄弟
All I ask is that you give it to Frick and Frack,
告诉他们这是你的血  然后就收手
tell them it's yours, stand back,
让他们来找我
and let them come to me.
我不得不承认  我很想看着他们俩送命
I can't deny I long to see those two digested
永远消失
once and for all.
就这么定了
You have a deal.
我猜你想签书面协议
I suppose you want it in writing?
我可不搞什么一"吻"为定
I don't kiss on the mouth.
那是你的损失
Your loss.
我正好有份标准的附加条款  就带在身上
I just so happen to have a standard rider...right here.
我很喜欢谈判的这个部分
I do so like this part.
你呢
Don't you?
[邪恶力量 第7季第23集]
好了  离出口还有三英里
All right. Exit's in 3 miles.
我还是觉得这是个馊主意
I still say this is a bad idea.
迪恩  这可是你的主意
Dean, it was your idea,
而且这是咱们俩想出最好的办法
and it was the best one either of us had.
我当时是当笑话讲的
I said it as a joke.
虽说这笑话不好笑  但个好主意
It was a bad joke -- good idea.
那还不是因为咱们没有魔咒  没有魔法书
Yeah, only because we got no magic spell, no book --
完全不知怎么找正直凡人之骨
nothing on how to find a freakin' righteous bone.
我们可以再召唤卡西迪奥
We can call Castiel again.
老兄  他光着屁股出现在我车里
Dude, on my car, he showed up naked...
还带来一群蜜蜂
covered in bees.
还好我没看见
Yeah, I'm not really sorry I missed that.
...在罗曼收购苏克农业公司后
...Right this time the stock is all-time high
公司股票一路高涨
following Roman's acquisition of SucroCorp.
要我说  跟着罗曼有肉吃
I say Roman's a buy.
这点我不赞同
Got to disagree with you there.
咱们还是走着瞧吧
I'm gonna call him a "Wait and watch."
拜托  洛夏  你想乐死我吗
Come on, Lawshe. You're killing me.
听我说完
Hear me out.
-这对罗曼来说是新领域  -是啊
- This is a new sector for Roman. - That's right.
他这会儿就在苏克农业总部呢
He's holed up at SucroCorp headquarters right now.
还是耐心等等
Just sit tight.
他在苏克农业总部
Holed up at SucroCorp, huh?
若甲方没有
"Should the party of the first part
将自己的意图告知乙方
fail to inform the party of the second part of his intent"
停
Pause right there.
说错了告诉我  这里该是乙方
Correct me -- that should be "Party of the second part
与甲方相关的人员
vis-a-vis party of the first party..."
我们不是刚修订过第314条的子条款A
'cause we just amended clause 314-sub-a.
没错
That's right.
专业点吧
You should do this professionally.
好的
Splendid.
好吧  若乙方...
So, "Should the party of the second part
咱们应该能在修道院找到正直之骨吧
I guess we can find a righteous bone of a freakin' nun and crap.
好吧  听听
All right. Here -- listen to this.
玛丽·本尼迪克特修女死于23岁
Sister Mary Benedict taught the learning-impaired
毕生教育有学习障碍的人
and died at age 23.
死得太早了
Eh, it's a little young.
找个活的长点的人
Find someone who's had time to cook.
好  还有个  有个玛丽·尤纳斯修女
Okay, well, there was, uh... here -- Sister Mary Eunice.
给穷人赊饭  60岁当上修道院院长
Uh, fed the poor, became Mother Superior at age 60.
一听就是有手段的人  权力腐化人心
Sounds political. Power corrupts.
好吧
Right. Um...
这个这个
Listen to this --
玛丽·康斯坦斯修女
Sister Mary Constant,
83年里默默无闻  谦逊有礼  心地善良
83 years of quiet, humble nun-like goodness.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
光读这个我就想做个正直的人了
Wow. I want to be more righteous just reading this.
没错
Exactly.
好吧  就她了
All right, well, I lay odds on her.
这边
Here we go.
好吧
Well...
把她的骨头挖出来吧
Let's bone this nun.
抱歉
Sorry.
在这种情况下  乙方
"...in which case, the party of the second part
放弃所有权力  无限期退居加拿大
forfeits all rights to Canada ad infinitum."
搞定了
I think we're done here.
苏珊
Susan!
什么事  先生
Yes, sir.
把克劳力先生手上合同复印三份
Take this from Mr. Crowley, make triplicates,
带笔和公证人过来
get pens and a notary.
我们准备签了
We're ready to sign this puppy.
他是想来个华丽丽的登场吗
Is he trying to make a grand entrance or...?
我也不知道
I don't...
混蛋  他放我们鸽子
Son of a bitch. He's standing us up.
但是我们召唤他了啊  他不是得...
Well, we summoned him. Doesn't he kind of have to --
如果克劳力想要耍你  他自有办法
If Crowley wants to screw you, he'll screw you.
说不定因为他有事来不了了
Or...he can't come 'cause something went wrong.
可能吧
Maybe.
说不定有好事呢
Maybe it's good news.
你们去搞定他  我没辙了
You deal with him. I can't anymore.
说明白点
You might want to be more specific.
我正在地球的另一半低调生活呢
I was laying low halfway across the world
那个情绪帝突然冒出来
when emo boy pops up out of nowhere
把我瞬间送回到这里
and zaps me right back here.
为什么
Why?
自己去问他
Come ask him.
他以前是你的好基友
He is your boyfriend first.
你好啊
Hey, there.
小卡  什么情况
So, Cass, what's, uh, what's the word?
迪恩  我一直在思考
Well, Dean, I've been thinking.
猴子真的很聪明  它们吃香蕉时
Monkeys are so...clever, and they're sensible
知道要剥皮  真明智
in that they leave the skins on the bananas that they eat.
真有必要拿它们试验化妆品吗
Is it really necessary to test cosmetics on them?
告诉我  迪恩  唇膏对你来说重要吗
I mean, how important is lipstick to you, Dean?
不重要
Not very.
进屋告诉我们发生了什么事  好吗
You want to come inside and, uh, tell us what's going on?
你们知道的
Now, you understand
我不参加暴力活动
I don't participate in aggressive activity.
是玛丽·康斯坦斯修女
Sister Mary Constant.
选得好
Good choice.
小卡  你去找梅格干嘛
Why'd you go to Meg, Cass?
我走后  我想去观察花朵和果实
When I left, I wanted to observe the flowers -- and fruit.
当然先看花了
Flowers come first, obviously.
但没有任何他们的消息
But I heard nothing from them.
谁的消息
You heard nothing from who?
卫戍队的人
The garrison.
卫戍队怎么了
What happened to the garrison?
我终于受不了这份静默
Well, finally, the silence was deafening,
就去一探究竟
so I went to look...
我去了先知家
To the home of the prophet.
利维坦可以杀死天使
You know, Leviathan can kill angels.
天父把它们关在炼狱中是有原因的
There's a reason why father locked them in purgatory.
他们就是会吃光整个水族箱的食人鱼
They're the... piranha that would eat the whole aquarium.
他们都死了
They're gone.
整个卫戍队  都死了
The entire garrison-- dead.
就算有人幸存  也躲起来了
If there's anyone left at all, they're in hiding.
抱歉打断
Um, I'm sorry.
如果天使都死了  那凯文哪去了
If the angels are dead, where's Kevin?
我可以把猴子从笼子里偷出来
I could steal them from their cages, the monkeys.
但我要把他们放在哪呢
But where would I put them all?
集中一点  凯文还活着吗
Hey! Focus. Is Kevin alive?
我不想吵架
I don't want to fight.
不  我不是
No, I'm not --
我们很担心
We're worried.
他们带走了他  他还活着
They took him. He's alive.
好沉的重担  但现在要你们来承担了
I felt such responsibility, but it's in your hands now.
-等等  等一下  -我轻松多了
- Wait. Hold on a freakin' minute. - I feel much better.
伙计们  那些是什么
Guys, what's all that?
我们召唤了克劳力
We called Crowley.
你们什么
You what?
别担心  他没出现
Don't worry. He never showed.
什么叫"没"
What do you mean "never"--
你看到他了吗  他放我们鸽子了
Do you see him anywhere? He stood us up.
深表遗憾  不过我要撤了
Well, I'm sorry about that, but I'm outie.
他还是可能
He could still sh--
随时出现
Show up at any time.
孩子们
Hello, boys.
真抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
真是各种尴尬啊
This is an embarrassment of riches.
留下来吧
Stay, won't you?
你已无处可逃
There's really nowhere to run.
想都别想化成黑烟逃跑  小猫咪
Don't even think of smoking out, pussycat.
我已经全面监控了这里
I've got eyes all over the place.
别动她
Leave her be.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
上次我们相见时  你奴役了我
When last we spoke, you-- well, enslaved me.
我很困惑  你怎么还没死
I'm confused. Why aren't you dead?
我也不知道
I...don't know.
你想死吗  我可以帮你哦
Well, do you want to be? 'cause I can help with that.
好了  够了
All right, enough.
我说够了才是够了
It's enough when I say.
我来这帮你们忙
I came here to help you.
却发现你们一直在骗我
I find out you've been lying to me,
窝藏天使  还不是随便哪一个天使
harboring an angel, and not just any angel--
是我最想剥皮拆骨的那个
the one angel I most want to crush between my teeth.
你现在都能杀死天使了
Oh, so you can crush angels now, huh?
你真无趣
You bore me. You know that?
毫无诗性
You have no sense of poetry.
你有什么要为自己辩解的
Now, what do you have to say for yourself?
我还在磨练我的沟通技巧
Well, I'm still, uh, honing my communication strategy.
我都没回过天堂
I haven't even been back to heaven.
我一直在想  天堂里没有昆虫
I keep thinking there are no insects up there,
但这里有数以万亿计的昆虫
but here we have... trillions.
他们能造出蜂蜜和丝绸
You know, they're making honey and silk
真是奇迹啊
and...miracles, really.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
比起天使我更喜欢昆虫
Um, preferring insects to angels, I guess.
给你  你喜欢的话  就送你一点意思意思
Here. I can offer a token, if you like.
这是蜂蜜
It's honey.
我亲自采集的
I collected it myself.
你精神错乱了
You're off your rocker.
他精神错乱了  是吧
He's off his rocker-- is that it?
真是因果报应啊
Karma's a bitch, isn't it?
你是来一雪前耻的
Look, did you come here to, uh, doggy-punch your old grudges
还是帮我们了结迪克的
or to help us end Dick?
选一个阵营吧
Pick a battle.
我很为难啊
Well, I'm vexed.
鱼和熊掌都想要呢
I'd like to do both.
打败这个疯子有什么意思
But where's the fun in clobbering a ball of wet fur?
等他恢复正常再给我短信吧
Text me when sparkles here retrieves his marbles, I suppose.
与此同时
Meanwhile...
送你们个礼物
...A prezzie.
真的假的  都打包好可以直接用了
Really? Just boxed-up and ready to go?
我是效率的典范
I'm a model of efficiency.
是吗
Is that right?
那你怎么迟到了
Then why were you late?
迪克把我关在恶魔陷阱里了
Dick had me in a devil trap.
他又不是傻子
He's not an idiot.
他知道你们俩想干什么
He knows what you two are after.
他给了你什么好处
So what did he offer you?
一个公平交易
A fair deal.
让我给你们错误的血
In exchange for giving you the wrong blood...
是恶魔的血  但是不是我的呢
It's demon, but is it mine?
是我的
It's my blood.
货真价实
Real deal.
我们为什么要相信你
And why should we trust you?
好家伙  别信  不要相信任何人
Good God, don't. Never trust anyone.
这是我从上一个合作伙伴那里学到的教训
A lesson I learned from my last business partner.
好吧
All right.
把血给我们
Give us the blood.
没问题
Certainly.
对了  还有个赠品
Oh, bonus.
梅格  我会把你掏空  带你回家
Meg, I'm gonna scoop you up, take you home,
烤得你外焦里嫩的
and roast you till you're jerky.
但...时机未到
But not...yet.
暂时让小卡留着你
Cass can have you for now.
可笑的是  看来你死了他会很难过
Hilariously, it seems he'd be upset at losing you.
而这俩小子还得靠小卡拿下迪克
And the boys need Cass to get Dick.
不是吗  小卡
Don't they, Cass?
我...我不再战斗了
Oh, I -- I don't fight anymore.
得了吧
Come on.
考虑到你对手的特点
Given the particulars of your enemy,
很不幸  你至关重要
sadly, you're vital.
见鬼
Son of a bitch!
纯铁  该死
Pure iron. Damn it.
好吧  怪我
All right. My mistake.
-该走了  -不
- Let's go. - No!
你离我远点
You stay away from me.
让我回家吧
Will you please let me go home?
(迪克·罗曼被评选为年度人物)
我需要你
I need you.
不
No.
待您批阅的PPT放您桌上了  先生
PowerPoint presetation's on your dest for approval, sir.
很好
Great.
苏珊  我看起来很傻吗
Susan, do I look like a fool?
-您这身形不会的  - 很好
- Not in that particular body, no. - Good.
我和你说过谈合约的三条定律吗
Have I told you there are three rules to contract negotiation?
保持口气清新  立下字据为证
Bring breath mints, get it in writing,
做好被人出卖的后备计划
and have a plan for when they screw you.
去冰柜一趟
Go to the freezer.
-取那个手臂吗  -没错  手臂  真乖
- The arm? - Yep, the arm. That a girl.
坐下
Sit.
待着
Stay.
我是凯文
I'm Kevin.
波利
Polly.
你来这干嘛
What are you doing here?
坐着
Sitting.
我想是吧
I guess.
你是先知吗
Are you a prophet?
这么说...
So...
我基本上得靠自己了
basically, I'm on my own, then.
有一点可以确定  我们只有一次机会
Well, one thing's for sure -- we only get one shot.
这玩意儿可无法重装
This thing don't reload.
你觉得克劳力会不会...
You think Crowley's, uh...
出卖我们
Double-crossing us?
对
Yeah.
你得弄明白他更想让谁死
You've got to figure who he wants dead more --
我们还是迪克
us or Dick.
那得看迪克给了他什么
Depends what Dick offered.
开始了
Here we go.
好的
Okay.
我们要...
Um, so do we, uh...
没有咒语可念  什么都没有
Uh, there's no magic words -- nothing.
你就倒血就是了
You just...just go.
那好吧
All right, then.
怎么没有雷电交加什么的
Where's all the thunder and lightning?
也许已经起作用了呢
Maybe it worked?
真是给力
Awesome.
这些不会令你们有任何不良反应
So, none of this should cause you any ill effect.
我在诺曼底的一个小农场找到的小麦
I went to a little farm in Normandy for the wheat
还有生菜和西红柿
and the lettuce and tomato and --
我还对猪进行了全面检验以及深切慰问
and I thoroughly examined and comforted the pig
然后才宰了它做火腿
before I...slaughtered it for the ham.
给  你们需要补充能量
Here. You need your strength.
谢谢  小卡
Thanks, Cass.
小卡  为什么克劳力那么确定
Hey, Cass, why was Crowley so certain
你需要和我们一起来
that you need to come with us?
克劳力错了  我会在这儿等
Crowley's wrong. I'll be waiting right here.
请你们接受三明治  这是我们团结的见证
But please -- accept this sandwich as a gesture of solidarity.
早上好  先生
Morning, Sir.
代表们正在路上
Delegates are on their way.
很好
Perfect.
我们得在他们到来之前让一切就绪
We're gonna want everything in place before they get here.
你去把保安叫进来
Send in the security detail, would you?
你好  罗曼先生
Hello, Mr. Roman.
靓表啊
Nice watch.
换好衣服
Get dressed.
为什么他要你...
Why does he want you to...?
我吃素
I'm a vegan.
准备好了吗  波利
You ready, Polly?
看到你们都来了我非常高兴
Well, I'm pleased as Punch to see you all here.
我们上次共处一室  还是在那个天使的体内
Last time we were in one room, it was inside that angel.
你们作为主力成员  我要你们跟上
Now, as key players, I need you up to speed
项目各方面的进度
on every aspect of the program,
而不仅仅限于
not just the sudden influx
各小区突然涌现的那些美味听话的猎物
of happy, delicious stoners in your neighborhood.
尽情吃吧
Oh. Eat up.
这寿司可是新鲜孤儿做成的
The sushi's made of fresh orphan.
好的
All righty.
屠宰场
The slaughterhouses --
尖端高效而又人性化
cutting-edge, humane, efficient.
首厂将于下月投入使用
First one goes online next month.
人群控制方面有什么策略
What's the crowd-control strategy?
问得好
Glad you asked.
我们在911报警电话等关键执法部门
We've laid employees at key junctures of law enforcement,
插入了自己的人
starting with the 911 call.
大家觉得有人照顾着他们  就不会恐慌
Everyone feels taken care of, everyone stays calm.
收获之前  我们再加大剂量
We'll up the dose just before harvest time.
他们什么都感觉不到的
They won't feel a thing.
(劳工  测试  牲畜)
我们分地区进行
We're taking a regional approach.
在俄亥俄州进行测试
Ohio -- beta-testing.
在威斯康辛州加工
Wisconsin -- processing.
在佛罗里达州繁殖
Florida -- breeding program.
翻到第10页
If you'll flip to page 10,
你会发现我们正大肆买下生育诊所
you'll see we're having a ball buying fertility clinics.
真是好东西
Real juicy stuff.
你怎么跑出笼子了  小耗子
Why are you out of your cage, mouse?
但现在我想和你们谈谈
But now I want to talk to you
一件让我激动不已的喜事
about something I'm really excited about.
各位
Everyone...
这位是波利
Meet Polly.
(苏克农业)
你收到图像了吗
You got it yet?
好了
Here we go.
不管你现在身在何处  多谢  查理
Thank you, Charlie, wherever you are.
看到你了  迪克
Got you, Dick.
这是二层的监控录像
Yeah, that's, uh, the second floor,
接下来是
and then --
这是怎么回事
What's that?
怎么可能
What the hell?
那个是迪克吗
Is that Dick?
那个也是迪克
And that's Dick.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
这三种癌症的遗传特性就是  发作迅速
So, genetic propensity for these three cancers -- zapped.
她现在浑浑噩噩  什么都不在乎
She's too stoned to care.
波利  脱掉你的裙子
Polly, take off your dress.
她看起来挺瘦的  不是吗
She's a slip of a thing, isn't she?
但吃的却像橄榄球中后卫一样多
And she eats like a linebacker.
总之  我们可不做艺术品
Bottom line -- we're not making art.
我们想要设计出完美的野兽
We want to engineer the perfect beast.
我们要吃肉  而这些瘦小的人
We want meat, and these zippy little hummingbirds
要尽快被淘汰掉
have to be bred out fast.
添加剂3.0
Additive 3.0.
请注意  我们运输的东西
Keep in mind, the stuff we're shipping --
会稀释一点  药效会慢些
a little diluted, longer-acting.
这就是添加剂3.0
Additive 3.0
只作用于我们想要消灭的特定人群之上
Targets only the characteristics we want to breed out.
将加在不含奶的咖啡伴侣和复合维生素中
It'll be added in nondairy creamer and multivitamins.
第一批货物明天就运往洛杉矶
First shipment heads to Los Angeles tomorrow.
注意看关于痢疾的报道
So watch those dysentery reports.
走之前  请去实验室参观一下
And stop by the lab before you go,
因为那些装咖啡伴侣的杯子可爱极了
'cause those creamer cups are just adorable.
重新播放一遍
Cycle through again.
那是汽车旅馆的女仆
That's the maid from the motel.
什么汽车旅馆
What motel?
哦  不
Oh, no.
鲍比  你想要做什么
Oh, Bobby, what are you doing?
等会  你是说鲍比
Wait. Are you saying that Bobby --
你等在这里
Look, just, uh, wait here.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?!
你有武器  盯着这一堆迪克吧
You got the weapon, and -- and eyes on Dick, plural.
我去搞定鲍比
I'll take care of Bobby.
萨姆
Sam! Hey!
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
鲍比
Bobby?
我知道你附身在她身上
I know you're in there.
听我说  这里到处都是监控录像
Listen to me. There are cameras everywhere.
那边就有一个
There's one right there.
停手吧  你会害死她的
Stop, okay? You're gonna get her killed.
鲍比  见鬼了
Bobby! Damn it!
你怎么能杀死迪克呢  你做不到的
How are you gonna kill Dick, huh? You can't!
对我来说这就足够了
Good enough for me.
不  我不会让你走的
No! I'm not letting you go.
-你走开  萨姆  -不
- Get out of here, Sam. - No.
鲍比  停手
Bobby, stop.
住手
Stop.
不
No!
好的  多谢
Okay, thanks.
她很好  今晚就能出院
She's fine. Checking out of the hospital tonight.
这可是好消息
Well, that's positive.
再说一遍你干嘛为个女仆掉头跑掉了
Tell me again why you turned tail for some maid.
你都到那里了啊
You were right there.
闭嘴  梅格
Shut up, Meg.
因为迪克制造了更多迪克
Because Dick made more Dicks.
他一定藏了一块原始的迪克·罗曼的躯体
He must've kept a chunk of the original Dick Roman somewhere.
让其他大嘴怪去摸了变身
They'd all have to touch it.
机灵鬼  你怎么了
Hey, shifty, what's your problem?
我们该养只猫
We need a cat.
你们不觉得这地方少了种生物吗
Doesn't this place feel one species short?
就迪克问题而言  你有何见解吗
You got anything to say on the topic of Dicks?
克劳力很肯定你能帮忙
Crowley was pretty sure that you could help.
我帮不上你们
I can't help.
明白吗  帮不了的
You understand? I can't.
我把一切都毁了
I destroyed...everything,
我只会再坏事
And I will destroy everything again.
我们别说了行吗
Can we please just leave it at that?
不
No.
-不行  -迪恩
- No, we can't. - Dean...
不能就这样完了
We can't leave it.
是你把这些怪物放进来
You let these friggin' things in.
你不能做三明治
So you don't get to make a sandwich.
你不能养猫
You don't get a damned cat.
没人在乎你是不是疯了  小卡
Nobody cares that you're broken, Cass.
你得收拾自己的烂摊子
Clean up your mess!
我说
You know...
我们该玩扭扭乐
We should play twister.
好极了
Nice.
你把我们唯一的希望吓跑了
You scared off the empire's only hope.
什么意思
Meaning?
你们没想过那些东西都在小卡肚子里待过吗
It occur to you every one of those things was in Cass?
他熟悉他们
He knows them.
他能看清他们的真实面目
He can see past the meat suits.
所以说他能认出哪个是真的假迪克·罗曼
So, he'll be able to spot the real...fake Dick Roman.
真该赏你朵小红花
Gold star, sugarpants.
要不是他疯了  你可能还有机会
Too bad he's froot loops. You might've had a chance.
看不出破绽的
There's no real point in looking for a tell.
他们都下载了迪克的思想
They all downloaded Dick's brain.
他们做什么都一样
They've all got the same tells.
好吧  那我们就想想
All right, then maybe the question is,
真正的迪克会做什么
what would the real Dick be doing?
你们就这点本事了吗
Is that the best you can do?
白痴
Idjits.
鲍比  我们不知道你是不是...
Bobby. We didn't know if you --
你们该想到
Well, you should've.
瓶子还在你们这儿呢
You got the flask.
俩傻缺
Dumb.
你们当时就该立刻给烧了
You should've burned it right off.
鲍比
Bobby --
我还是特别想回去
I'm still jonesing to go back...
随便抓个可怜人来
grab some poor bastard,
附在他身上去找迪克
kamikaze 'em going after Dick.
情况很糟
It's bad.
美国是进取人士的天堂
America is for go-getters.
亲力亲为  就能创造奇迹
Folks who get off their butts and make it happen.
我们面对现实吧
Let's be real.
我差点杀了你
I damn near killed you.
还有那个女士
And that woman.
那不怪你  鲍比  真不能怪你
It wasn't your fault, Bobby -- not really.
是啊
Right.
鬼魂就这样
That's just what ghosts turn into.
我还真以为自己不会那么愚蠢
I really bet the farm I could outsmart that.
那是什么感觉
So, what's it feel like?
什么  心怀怨念吗
What? Going vengeful?
就像怎么挠都觉得痒
It's an itch you can't scratch out.
听我说
Look...
我完了
I'm done.
去抓迪克吧
Go get Dick.
但是别为了一己私仇
But don't do it 'cause you think it'll scratch the itch.
把这当做你们份内的事
Do it 'cause it's the job.
等你们的时候到了
And when it's your time...
别留恋人世
Go.
敬
Here's to...
跟你们在另一边相见
running into you guys on the other side.
不过
Only...
别来的太早了
Not too soon.
好吗
All right?
小卡  我需要人帮助
Cass, I need a wingman.
-迪恩  -你不想去寻死
- Dean... - You don't want to jump into the jaws of death,
我理解
That's...fine.
能去办点小事行吗
How about we run a little errand?
谢谢你送我
Thanks for the lift.
不客气
My pleasure.
迪恩
Dean...
小卡  我们说过了
Cass, we've been over it.
我懂  你帮不上忙
I get it -- you can't help.
如果我们去攻击迪克却失手
If we attack Dick and fail,
你和萨姆就光荣牺牲  对吗
then you and Sam die heroically, correct?
或许吧
I don't know. I guess.
最好的结果  我为了弥补我愚蠢的过失而死
And at best, I die trying to fix my own stupid mistake.
或者  我不死  又再次活过来
Or...I don't die -- I'm brought back again.
我现在懂了  复活就是惩罚
I see now. It's a punishment resurrection.
一次比一次糟
It's worse every time.
抱歉  你说的是上帝吗
I'm sorry. Uh, we're talking about god crap, right?
我就是个灾星  迪恩
I'm not good luck, Dean.
好吧  你知道吗
Yeah, but you know what?
如果到了最后
Bottom of the ninth,
我就只剩你了
and you're the only guy left on the bench...
那抱歉  你是不是灾星我都要你
Sorry, but I'd rather have you, cursed or not.
再说  少唧歪了
And anyway, nut up, all right?
我们都是灾星
We're all cursed.
你看我像招财猫吗
I seem like good luck to you?
怎么了
What?
我不想让你不舒服
Well, I don't want to make you uncomfortable,
但我听你有原谅我的意思
but I detect a note of forgiveness.
反正我明天可能会死掉  何不呢
Yeah, well, I'm probably gonna die tomorrow, so...
我跟你一起去
Well, I'll go with you.
我会尽力而为
And I'll do my best.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么
So...
能问问计划是什么吗
Can I ask the plan?
听克劳力的意思  迪克知道我们要来
Well, according to Crowley, dick knows we're coming,
那我们就高调入场
so we're gonna announce ourselves -- big.
回见了  二货
Later, ho nuggets.
地狱之王要见你
The king of hell will see you now.
凯文  伙计
Kevin. Hey, buddy.
我能得快点走
We got to hustle, okay?
等等  我们还不能走
Wait. We can't leave yet.
没啥不能的  没事的  我们得走了
Uh, yeah, we can. It's okay. We got to go.
你不懂  迪克的实验室里有咖啡伴侣
You don't understand. Dick's got creamer in his lab.
-他要杀掉所有的瘦子  -啥  慢点说
- He's gonna kill all the skinny people. - Wait. What? Slow down.
我们得去炸实验室  萨姆
We have to blow up the lab, Sam.
求你了
Please.
好吧  我们走
Yeah, fine. Let's go.
要知道  我觉得这会成为
You know, I think this might end up
史上最丝滑可口的种族灭绝
the slickest little genocide in history.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
说说而已
Just sayin'.
看来该给你升职了
I smell "promotion."
真唐突  不过无所谓了
Little abrupt... but okay.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
很高兴又见面了
Good to see you again.
谢谢你载我们去天堂
Thanks for the ride into paradise.
你也不赖啊
And good on you!
居然都找齐了  优加
Pulling that together -- A-plus.
你觉得这东西不好使  对吗
Oh, you don't think this'll work, do you?
你信那个恶魔
You trust that demon?
你确定我是我吗  迪恩
You sure I'm even me, Dean?
不
No.
但他确定
But he is.
跟克劳力打交道就要注意这点
See, here's the thing when dealing with Crowley --
他总是能找机会占你便宜
he will always find a way to bone you.
我要走了
This meeting's over.
你真以为你能战胜我吗
Did you really think you could trump me?
说实话
Honestly?
不
No.
我就想我得趁你不备
Figured we'd have to catch you off guard.
萨姆  我们得走了
Sam, we should go.
搞毛啊
What the hell?
随时都会有更多的大嘴怪来  萨姆
More chompers any second, Sam.
别担心
Not to worry.
我有一小支恶魔军队在外面候着
I have a small army of demons outside.
毕竟斩其首  躯体挣扎凌乱
Cut off the head, and the body will flounder, after all.
想想要是自古以来你就这么一个王
Think if you'd had just one king since before the first sunrise.
你现在肯定也很凌乱
You'd be in a kerfuffle, too.
这就是你想要的
Which is exactly what you wanted.
你也是
So did you.
没有个大点的计划  利维坦不过是怪物乙罢了
Without a master plan, the Levis are just another monster.
虽然不好干掉  但你就喜欢有挑战性的
Hard to stomp, sure, but you love a challenge.
你的职责是让他们群龙无首
Your job is to keep them from organizing.
迪恩呢
Where's Dean?
那个骨头  有个小副作用
That bone... has a bit of a kick.
上帝的武器常这样
God weapons often do.
真该在盒子上标出警告
They should put a warning on the box.
他们去哪了  克劳力
Where are they, Crowley?!
帮不了你  萨姆
Can't help you, Sam.
抱歉了  先知我带走了
Sorry, Sam. Prophet's mine.
你得到了你想要的
You got what you wanted --
迪克死了  又拯救了世界
Dick's dead, saved the world.
所以我要把先知带走
So I want one little prophet.
抱歉了
Sorry, moose.
可惜帮不了你
Wish I could help.
你现在还真是有一堆麻烦
You certainly got a lot on your plate right now.
看来你这次真的是
It looks like you are well and truly...
得独自面对了
on your own.
醒醒
Wake up.
很好
Good.
我能得出去
We need to get out of here.
我们在哪
Where are we?
你不知道吗
You don't know?
我只记得我们宰了迪克
Last I remember, we ganked Dick.
他死后会去哪呢
And where would he go in death?
等等  你不是说
Wait. Are you telling me...?
这里的每个灵魂都是怪兽
Every soul here is a monster.
他们来这儿永远地折磨彼此
This is where they come to prey upon each other for all eternity.
我们在炼狱
We're in purgatory?
我们怎么出去
How do we get out?
恐怕我们要被人碎成碎片了
I'm afraid we're much more likely to be ripped to shreds.
小卡  我想我们还是
Cass, I think we'd better --
小卡
Cass?